人人影視
YYeTs.com
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯： 暴龍蛋     圈圈     阿髻
翻譯： 蘇小黛     Kiko     DustD
時間軸： 濃子   萌    校對： 蘇小黛
后期： 孤帆    總監： 米小勒   胖兔純
塞勒姆
第一季  第六集
《塞勒姆》前情提要
Previously on "Salem"...
把那些畫面再跟我描述一次
Tell me again of the visions.
在歷史上
Has thought to be present
每次大祭典中都會出現
at every grand rite throughout history.
你竟然威脅我  你唯一真正的盟友
You would threaten me, your one true ally?
這么說其他人都已背叛我了
So the others have turned on me.
沒錯
Yes.
蘿絲
Rose?
每個人
Everyone.
我在想
I wonder.
想什么
Wonder what?
如果他當初沒走
If he'd never left,
奧登上尉對你還會有這么大吸引力嗎
would Captain Alden still hold such desperate appeal?
告訴我約翰·奧登的秘密
Tell me John Alden's secret.
我們有過約定
We had a deal.
那約定已經無法使我滿足
Our deal no longer pleases me.
你想要什么
What do you want?
我想變成和你一樣
I want to be just like you.
惡靈現已落入旁人之手
The malum has fallen into other hands.
這是邪惡之物
This object is evil.
它為惡魔回歸祝圣
It consecrates the earth for the devil's return.
你們兩個王八蛋
You filthy pricks.
膽小鬼
You coward!
還在等什么
What are we waiting for?
土星...
Saturn...
巫師界的行星統治者
...planetary ruler of witches.
你喝多了吧
Have you been drinking?
當然了
Most certainly.
靠這種傻瓜陷阱抓住巫師
It's not every night I catch a witch
可不是常有的事兒  你說呢
with a... a "Boob's trap" was it?
用你那裝著惡靈的盒子
Lured here by that infernal box of yours,
做誘餌
the malum.
每隔17年  土星正好會...
Once every 17 years, Saturn stations direct...
運行到它的宮位上停留片刻
...exalted in its own house for a few brief moments.
這次就在今天傍晚
This will happen today at nightfall.
關我們什么事
And we care because?
在這種情況下
A witch suspended beneath saturn
把巫師吊在木星宮位的正下方
as it stations direct, exalted in its own house,
他們就不能說謊了
cannot lie.
據可靠消息說這就是
Reputable sources say it is why
奧德修斯在賽斯島上待了那么久的原因
Odysseus himself dallied so long on Circe's Island.
淘氣的小子
Naughty lads.
我們得把她拖到樹林里去
We must haul her out into the woods...
你們會被懲罰的
You need to be punished.
讓她處于土星宮正下方...
...bend her beneath saturn as it stations direct...
然后審問她
And interrogate the witch.
我已經計算出精確的地點
I've calculated the precise spot,
但首先我們得保證她能順利抵達
but first we must secure her for travel.
為什么我家到處都是
Why does my house smell
一股野狗的尿騷味兒
like a pack of wild dogs pissed all over it?
這是什么
What is this?
狗尿
Canis urinam...dog piss.
加上一些草藥
Plus some medicinal plants.
藜蘆  龍葵  血根草
Hellebore, nightshade, bloodroot...
混合起來就是一種強力麻醉劑
In combination, the result is a powerful paralytic.
幫我拿著
Hold this.
皮下注射
Hypodermic.
牛逼吧
Ingenious, eh?
這是個非凡的時代  上尉
We live in remarkable times, captain.
每天都有新發現  新發明
New discoveries, new inventions every day.
新武器...  去對抗舊日的敵人
New weapons... to fight an old enemy.
有種下來啊  黑暗在等著你們呢
Come on down, boys. The darkness is waiting for you.
我們得把這藥劑注射到她的靜脈里
We need to inject this mixture into her veins.
準備好
Get ready.
過來點
Come closer.
黑暗將吞噬你
The darkness wants to taste you.
按住她
Hold her still!
約翰
John!
兒子
Son!
你為什么要這么對我
Why are you doing this to me?
-母親  -好痛
- Mother? - It hurts so!
她在地獄里呢  上尉
She's in hell, captain.
她是惡魔們最愛的妓女
She's the devil's favorite whore.
她愛死那里了
She loves it there.
不  上尉  別啊  扎錯地方就完了
No, captain, don't! It has to be precise!
還真行
That will do.
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*Witch drums*
*擂我戰鼓*
*Pound me the witch drums*
*鼓鳴震天*
*The witch drums*
*寧入地獄*
*Better pray for hell*
*不留人間*
*Not hallelujah*
怕她偷銀器嗎
Afraid she'll steal the silver?
她真是個邋遢鬼
She is a dirty little creature.
你剛帶我來這兒的時候  我不也一樣嗎
So was I when you first brought me here.
你準備什么時候殺了她
When are you going to kill her?
幫她凈身  給她找件干凈衣服穿上
Clean her up. Give her something to wear.
其他東西全燒了
And burn all her things.
她再也用不著了
She won't be needing them anymore.
老實說
Truth be told,
我真想看看她的大腦
I long for a good look at her brain.
還大腦  我連她臉都不忍直視好嗎
Her brain? I can barely look at her face.
我相信我們的行為
I believe that our abilities
是受我們大腦支配的
are regulated by our brains.
我想知道魔鬼是不是從實質上改變了她
I wonder if the devil has changed her somehow materially.
可能她大腦的某個區域異常增大
Perhaps some region of her brain is abnormally enlarged.
也可能是你腦袋有問題吧
Or perhaps some region of yours.
快點  否則我們就活不到明天了
Hurry, or we'll be dead before tomorrow.
好好看著  孩子
Observe, child,
忠誠婚姻的真諦
the quintessence of devoted marriage,
我是多么悉心照料我丈夫梳洗
how carefully I attend to my dear husband's toilet...
他又是怎樣毫不畏懼地
...and how fearlessly
把自己的脖子暴露于我的刀下
he exposes his throat to my blade.
來吧  梅西小姐
Come along, Miss Mercy.
讓她留下
Leave her.
你帶他走吧  緹圖芭
Take him with you, Tituba.
一個人太少  三個就太多了
One's too few, and three's too many.
你的眼中...
Your eyes...
充滿了欲望
So filled with want.
最難的不是得到你想要的  孩子
The hard part's not getting what you want, child.
而是知道你想要什么
The hard part's knowing what you want.
我知道
But I do.
我知道自己想要什么
I do know what I want.
是啊  你就想變得跟我一樣
Mm, of course... to be just like me.
有一天吧
Someday.
我希望有一天可以
I hope I may be.
心懷希望地享受旅途比到達目的地要好
Well, it's better to travel hopefully than to arrive.
給你講個故事
A story?
好啊  請講吧
Why, yes, please.
我很久沒聽故事了
I haven't heard one in such a long time.
我母親去世后就沒聽過
Not since my mother died.
是啊
No.
清教徒的長老們根本不在意故事
Puritan fathers don't care much for stories.
是我們女人讓故事得以流傳的
We women keep them alive.
對
Yes.
我最喜歡的故事都在這本書上
This one has all my favorites.
你想看的話可以借給你
You may borrow it, if you like.
不
No.
父親說女孩子不需要識字讀書
Father says girls have no need to learn to read.
他只讀那本唯一值得讀的書
He would read the only book worth reading
并且讀給我聽
and read it to me.
然后  有一天
And then, one day,
他會找個合適的人替他給我讀書
he would find the right man to take over the job.
這是上帝的旨意
God's will.
我的神可不是這樣
Not my god.
我信仰的神希望我們自己讀書
Mine likes us to read for ourselves.
有時間我教你識字讀書吧
Perhaps I shall teach you to read someday.
現在呢  我就先給你講一個
In the meantime, I'll tell you one...
我記得的故事
...from memory...
是講  暗夜女王
about...the queen of the night
以及她是怎樣成為女王的故事
and how she became queen.
并非所有的女王天生就是公主
Not all queens start as princesses.
有的出身貧寒
Some begin in ashes.
沒錯
Indeed.
開始了
Okay.
很久很久以前  有一個少女
Once upon a time, there lived a maiden,
秀發漆黑如夜
hair as black as night...
皮膚白皙似雪
...skin as white as snow.
這個少女  愛上了一個英俊的王子
And the maiden, she loved a handsome prince.
王子也愛她
And the prince loved her.
來
Come.
好
Okay.
但是有一個邪惡的國王
But there was an evil king,
他故意讓王子去送死
and he sent the prince to his death.
而那個可憐的少女
And the poor maiden,
她萬念俱毀心如死灰
her heart turned gray as ash.
一天晚上  她絕望之際
One night, in her despair,
一個仙女找到了她
a fairy came to her
并且向她承諾  如果她放棄
and promised her that all the world would be hers
對已故王子的最后一絲愛意
if she would but give up the last of her love
那整個世界都將是她的
for her dead prince.
雖然她不想失去身體里
And though she wept to lose the only part of him
王子僅剩的血脈...
that still lived deep inside her...
但她還是照仙女說的做了
she did as she was told...
只希望她的夢想有一天能實現
in the hopes that all her dreams might still come true.
說來也巧
And so it came to pass
可憐的少女恰好被帶到了那個國王的城堡
that the ash maiden was brought to the king's castle.
在那里  一個仆人將她匆匆帶進城堡
There, she met a servant who hurried her inside.
通過碗碟儲藏室的門
And through the scullery door,
她看到各路領主官員
she watched the lords and ladies of the land
在跟邪惡的國王和王后
enjoy a sumptuous feast
盡情享受豐盛的酒宴
with the evil king and his queen.
就是這場酒宴上
And at this feast,
一個黑暗的王子趁無人注意時
a dark prince slew the old queen
手輕輕一搖  便把年邁的王后殺死了
with an invisible wave of his hand...
這是在為少女
...clearing the way
掃清障礙  以便她成為王后
for the ash maiden herself to become queen.
她成功了嗎
And did she?
什么成功了
Did she what?
成功成為王后了嗎
Become queen?
成功了
Yes.
但你知道做王后的代價是什么嗎
But you know the worst part about becoming queen?
什么
What?
你得嫁給國王
It often requires marrying a king.
于是少女嫁給了邪惡的國王  成為王后
And so the ash maiden married the evil king and became queen,
大婚之夜  處處歡聲笑語
her wedding night a consummation of joy and pleasure.
但歡樂不屬于她
But none of it hers.
當晚  一個魔鬼重壓在她身上
That night, she felt one monster on top of her
另一個則潛藏在她心里
and another inside.
她瞥見自己的靈魂面目全非
And she glimpsed what her soul was becoming
也學會了作為王后的第一課
and learned her first lesson as queen...
不要輕易許愿
be careful what you wish for.
她以王后之身侍奉邪惡的國王
She served as the queen to the evil king
短短兩年  仿若兩千年之久
for two years that felt like 2,000.
當她再也無法忍受之時
But when she could take no more,
她乞求仙女將她變回當初的少女
she begged the fairy to turn her back into the ash maiden.
但仙女拒絕了
But the fairy refused
轉而向她展示了遼闊的王國
and showed her all the kingdom that lay before her
并告訴她一切皆可握在手中
and said all this might still be hers.
你知道為什么麥哲家  西布里家
You know why the Mathers and the Sibleys
奧登家  以及這些最早踏足塞勒姆的家族
and the Aldens and the other founding families
會選擇這片土地作為他們新的圣地
really picked this spot to be their new Jerusalem?
這座小鎮將成為世上最富庶的地區之一
This town will become one of the richest on earth.
執掌塞勒姆的人  將掌控新的世界
And who controls Salem controls the new world.
少女明白自己已無路可退
The ash maiden understood there was no turning back.
她要接受王后的身份
She would embrace her role as queen
以及隨之而來的力量
and all the power that came with it.
那晚  她要第一次動用那股力量
That night, for the first time, she would use that power.
也是那晚
And that night,
整個世界開始顛倒了
the whole world began to turn upside-down.
別再耍花招了  丫頭
Stop your silly games, girl.
快過來
Come here.
這一吻
For it was not by a kiss
她不能將青蛙變成王子
she might make a frog into a prince,
卻能將國王變成蟾蜍
but by a kiss she might make a king into a toad.
甚至是...
Or even...
我得把你綁起來
I must bind you.
但即使綁起來
Ah, but even bound...
你也還是太強健了
You are far too much man for me.
我需要幫手一起對付你
I need some help to handle you.
你喜歡玩游戲嗎  喬治
Do you like games, George?
喜歡  我喜歡
Yeah. Yeah.
-喜歡嗎  -喜歡
- You like games? - Yes.
于是王后開始
And so the queen came to rule
將國王和王國操縱于股掌之間
the king and all his kingdom,
那晚  她成了真正的暗夜女王
and thus became the queen of the night.
從此過上了幸福快樂的生活
And so she lived happily ever after.
我們怎么會在這里
But how... how are we here?
我們在樹林里
We're...in the woods.
可剛剛還在房間里  你還鎖上了門
We were in your room. You locked the door.
通往各處自有門路
There are many doors to many places...
對巫師而言
for a witch.
我沒說你是巫師
I never said you were that.
我從未指認你
I-I'd never point my finger at you.
我發誓
I swear.
我沒有  我不會的
I wouldn't. I-I won't.
沒有
No.
你當然不會
You most certainly won't.
做得好  我的小獵手
Well done, my little hunter.
飽食此物  我也將生出翅膀飛往南方
Enough of these, and I, too, will grow wings and fly south.
樹林里只有兩種生物
You only meet two kinds of creatures in the woods...
獵手和獵物
the hunters and the hunted.
感謝明月  我們是獵手
Thank the moon we are what we are.
至少今天還是
At least for today.
烏林鸮的叫聲
The call of a great gray owl,
土星的吉物
Saturn's mascot.
時辰快到了
It's nearly time.
快點
A bit faster.
已經很近了
It's nearly in position.
我們必須位于土星的正下方
We must be directly beneath Saturn.
然后如何
Then what?
我們將得到唯一的機會
Then we get the one chance,
那一刻我們提出問題  得到答案
a moment to ask our questions and receive the answers.
然后得在麻醉藥效褪去之前把她殺了
Then we must kill her before the paralytic wears off.
要么就被她殺死
Or she kills us.
這種情況更有可能發生
That would be the most likely outcome.
希望你的燧火槍能幫上忙
I presume your flintlock will do the trick.
幫不了
Unless it doesn't.
用槍相當于把命運系于武器之上
A gun puts all your faith in the weapon,
而非自己手里
not the hand.
要么開火  要么不開
It either fires, or it don't.
十次有八會奏效
8 out of 10 times, it works.
但我們不能冒險去賭
But I don't think we can afford that gamble.
那么一把利劍如何
Then how about a sword?
我很驚訝  麥哲
You surprise me, Mather.
我在學校修過一些劍術
I fenced a little at school.
水準如何
Any good?
神學班里最可懼的對手
The most fearsome in all the divinity class.
好吧
Well...
這個正合適
This just may do.
我去開
I shall get it.
怎么了
What is it?
死亡之神不見了
The samhain is missing.
什么
What?
父親找西布里夫人的侍女來干什么
Why would father be meeting with Mrs. Sibley's servants?
只有上帝才知道了
The good lord knows.
肯定是又有"森意"了吧
More "Busy-ness," I'm sure.
真不知道這世界都怎么了
I swear I don't know what this world comes to.
人人都執迷于各自的"森意"
Everyone is all to obsessed with their "Busy-ness."
這是未來  母親
It's the future, mother.
從遙遠的地方運來東西  又送去更遠的地方
Bringing goods from far away, taking them on still further,
這開啟了新世界的大門
It opens new worlds.
還有  母親  是"生意"不是"森意"
And it's "Business," Mother, not "Busy-ness."
我聽起來沒什么兩樣
It's all "Busy-ness" To me.
現在  告訴他
Now tell him.
說  說這就是你想要的
Say it .. this is what you want.
是  是  是
Yes! Yes! Yes!
整個世界都將是你的
All the world shall be yours.
我們快到了
We're nearly in position...
就在亂葬崗邊上
Just past the crag.
到了
This is it.
就是這里
We do it here.
這兒
Here?
我是不是該感謝你
I guess I should be grateful you brought me
只把我帶到了世上第二惡心的地方
To the second most unpleasant place I've ever seen.
這還真是審訊犯人的好地方  麥哲
Great place to interrogate a prisoner, Mather.
這可不是我選的
It's not I who pick.
得怪該死的土星
The old bastard saturn himself,
偏偏運行到了這里
he's right overhead.
我們得在這兒把她弄起來  就現在
We must raise her here and now.
把她掛在那棵樹下  就天空正下方那棵
Suspend her from that tree directly beneath the sky
等土星來讓她松口
And let the planet loosen her tongue.
咱們的蘿絲小姐怎么樣了
How is our Miss Rose holding up?
眼都沒眨過一下
Hasn't blinked an eye.
很好
Good.
那就好
That's good.
快  只有一分鐘了
Hurry. Just a minute to go.
麻醉藥效在消褪
The paralytic is wearing off!
好吧
Okay. All right.
我們要錯過時辰了
We're losing the moment!
拉
Pull!
好了  這應該能撐住
There. That should hold it.
只要再過半刻  她就不得不開口了
Just a half moment more, and then she must speak!
謝謝  還能再來點嗎
Thank you, sir. May I have some more?
-天啊  -來吧  再來一次
- God.  - Again. Do it again.
小子  黑暗會把你們吞噬的
The darkness is going to eat you little men.
看在上帝的份上
For the love of christ.
把你倆的妓女帶來
Bring 'round your two whores.
我們就可以開派對了
Oh, we will have a party.
格里安娜和瑪麗·西布里
Gloriana and Mary Sibley.
你逃離了大惡人喬治·西布里
You ran away from big, bad George Sibley,
你害怕他的勢力
Afraid of what he might do.
可憐的瑪麗無處可逃
Poor Mary had nowhere to run.
她只能用自己唯一擁有的東西
She faced down the puritans
去對抗清教徒...
with the only thing that she had...
就是她兩腿間的那個無底洞
That bottomless pit between her thighs.
而你那時在哪里呢  奧登上尉
And where were you, Captain Alden?!
奧登  等等
Alden, wait!
等等
Wait!
這就對了
Yes!
該死的  快說  土星將強迫你說出實話
Speak, damn you! Saturn compels you to the truth!
你想知道什么
What would you know?
一切
Everything.
南方  我的朋友們
South, my friends.
很快  我們將飛去南方
Someday soon, we will fly south.
那里沒有清教徒  也沒有雪
No puritans there and no snow.
就像毛毯里的跳蚤  我們會感到...溫暖
Like a flea in a blanket we will be...warm.
你去到比那還溫暖的地方
You will go someplace far warmer than that
如果你忘了到底誰是主子  老狐貍
If you don't remember who's in charge, cunning man.
行動如此悄無聲息
Almost as quiet in her movements
都快跟她主子差不多了
As the mistress herself.
瑪麗·西布里會的一切都是我教的
I taught Mary Sibley everything she knows.
那學徒超越主人的概率又有多大呢
And how often it is that apprentice surpasses master.
閉嘴
Silence!
死亡之神失蹤了
The Samhain is missing.
她不在塞勒姆
She's not in salem.
一定是在這樹林里  你的樹林
She must be in these woods... your woods.
我們沒見過她
We have not seen her.
我們今晚的確在樹林里看到一個女巫
We did see a witch in the woods tonight,
但不是蘿絲小姐
But not Miss Rose.
是你的主子  你親手教出來的那位
Your mistress, the one you taught everything,
很明顯你還教了她
Including, apparently,
如何給自己開路
how to make her own doors.
小心點  老狐貍
Take care, cunning little man.
這可是個危險的世界
It's a dangerous world.
記住你是站在哪邊的
Remember whose side you're on.
什么是大祭典
What is the grand rite?
死亡
Death.
誰的死亡
For who?
你  還有所有像你一樣的人
For you and all like you.
為什么
Why?
為你們以前所做的事
For all you've done
并阻止你們將會做的事
And to stop all you will do.
怎么做
How?
無辜之血
Cruor innocentia.
向我們的主
Sacrifices consecrate
獻上祭祀的貢品
the land to our lord.
無辜之血
Cruor innocentia.
"無辜者的鮮血"
"Innocent blood."
祭品
Sacrifices.
那你們還沒有開始動手
Then you have not yet begun.
我們已經開始了
We have begun.
無辜者的鮮血四濺
Innocent blood flows.
并沒有不明原因死亡
There have been no unexplained deaths,
沒有孩童失蹤
no missing children.
你們不可能已經殺了人作祭品
You can have committed no sacrifices.
只要造成了痛苦就算祭祀
It's not a sacrifice unless it hurts.
你痛苦嗎  麥哲
Are you hurting, Mather?
她在說什么
What is she saying?
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
柯頓  我們得殺了她
Cotton, we have to kill her.
不  快告訴我你是什么意思
No. You tell me what you mean!
你們以為可以把我像垂線木偶一樣掛著嗎
You think you can dangle me like a puppet?
你們才是木偶  你們所有人  木偶
You're the puppets, all of you... puppets!
【咒語】
Neopheyn!
Barbas!
【咒語】
Aligon!
Anaboth!
【咒語】
Madicon!
Furcas!
她的咒語召喚來了死人
Her spell has raised the dead!
我找到你了
So, I have found you.
我欠你太多了
I owe you so much.
我記得所有你教過我的事
I remember all you taught me...
如何像清教徒一樣思考
how to think like a puritan,
如何看穿他們貪婪的雙眼
to see through their greedy eyes...
在他們眼中  這些森林就是待建的
these woods were really mighty ships
巨大船只和房屋
and houses in the making...
還有我們將如何
and how, one day,
在將來某天用他們難填的欲壑來還治其身
we would use their unquenchable desire to seize control.
一切都在按計劃進行著
All goes exactly as planned.
但你卻未經我同意
And yet, you brought the malum to salem
把惡靈帶到了塞勒姆
without my knowledge.
為什么  蘿絲
Why, Rose?
約翰·奧登
John Alden.
他只是個男人
He is just a man.
我不再是一個會被男人迷倒的小女孩了
I am no mere girl to fall to pieces for a man.
真正的邪惡
True malice,
像那種驅動著大祭典的力量
like that which powers the grand rite,
要醞釀在沒有情感的心里才是最佳
ferments best in a loveless heart.
我看過你的內心
I have looked into your heart,
那里可不缺少愛意
and it is anything but loveless.
你仍然愛著約翰·奧登
You still love John Alden.
我不能冒這個險
I couldn't take the chance.
所有的這一切
There is no part of all this,
從你心碎到大祭典
from your broken heart to the grand rite itself,
都在我計劃之中
that I have not planned.
是我向喬治·西布里灌輸了
I put the very thought in George Sibley's head
他必須把約翰·奧登遣走的想法
that he ought to to send John Alden away.
是你
It was you.
沒有哪一步是我沒預見到的
Not a step have I not foreseen,
包括你帶那個姑娘到樹林里來
Right down to your bringing the girl here to the woods
要殺掉她的事
to kill her.
那你呢
And you.
你怎么會來這里
How came you to be here?
我故意讓自己被他們倆
Ah, I allowed myself to be captured
抓住并審問
and interrogated by them.
是嗎
Oh, really?
為什么呢
Why?
為了徹底弄明白
To find out, once and for all,
約翰·奧登心里怎么想的
what is in John Alden's heart.
你該感到榮幸
You should be flattered.
你已經成了這樣
All you've become...
那個可憐的傻瓜
The poor fool,
他依然愛你并且會一直愛著
he still loves you and always will.
但是我需要你的心
But I need your heart.
我需要它破碎
I need it broken.
沒有比死亡更能令人心碎的了
And nothing breaks the heart like death.
我只不過幫塞勒姆省去了
I merely saved Salem the cost
運送他倆的尸體到亂葬崗的費用
and your Isaac the trouble
也省得你那個艾薩克再跑一趟了
of transporting their bodies to the crag.
你見過我們新加入的姐妹了嗎
Have you met our newest sister?
怎么
What?
我記得你說過
I thought you said
土星會迫使她說出真相
Saturn would compel her to speak the truth.
沒錯
It did.
什么真相
What truth?
我只聽到了謎語
I heard only riddles.
有時候  真相就是一個謎語
Sometimes, the truth is a riddle.
那謎底呢
And the answer?
不知道
I don't know.
我得思考再思考
I must think and then think again.
與此同時  那個...
In the meantime,that...
怪物依然逍遙在外
creature is still out here.
我有好幾年的時間經常獨自夜宿樹林
I spent most nights for many a year alone in the woods
雖然知道在每片陰影  每棵樹后都有人
Knowing there was someone ready to slit my throat
時刻準備著割斷我的喉嚨
in every shadow, behind every tree,
但人始終還是要睡覺的
but you still got to sleep.
再說  她不會再在塞勒姆露面了
Besides, she won't show her face again in Salem.
她知道到時候連審判都不會有
She knows she wouldn't even rate a trial.
她會被直接上套索  筆直下地獄
Straight to the noose, straight to hell.
我真欽佩你的"sangfroid"
I admire your sangfroid.
就是法語的"冷血"
French for "Cold blood."
這里是褒義詞
It's a compliment.
謝了
Thanks.
我則欽佩你的...
I admire your...
別催我  我會想出點什么的
Hey, don't hurry me. I'll think of something.
你進樹林的時候是個書呆子
Well, you came into these woods a bookworm.
走出去的時候就是個獵人了
You're walking out a hunter.
一個沒有收獲的獵人
A hunter without a catch.
這也不錯啊
Ah, yeah, but that's good...
一個饑餓的獵人
A hungry hunter.
這才是最危險的
That's the most dangerous kind.
奧登上尉
Captain Alden.
麥哲牧師
Reverend Mather.
晚上好  西布里夫人
Evening, Mrs. Sibley.
你這么晚還出來
You're out late.
我經常失眠
I'm often sleepless.
而我發現  夜晚的氣息使我平靜
And I find the...night air calms me.
你倆呢
And you two?
我們只是在觀測
We were just...tracking
土星逆行的天象軌道
the retrograde movement of saturn.
開始關注占星術了嗎  上尉
Taken up astrology, captain?
俗話說得好
You know what they say.
一切都是星座惹的禍
The fault's not in us but the stars.
我覺得你把這話記反了
I think you may have that the wrong way around.
祝你倆晚安
Good night to you both.
我本想問你今晚到底發生了什么
I would ask what really happened to you tonight.
但是
But?
你絕對不會告訴我
You'd never tell me.
我了解你
I know you.
送你回家吧
Walk you home?
見到了黑暗之人  對吧
Met the dark man, did you?
和我們一伙了  是吧
One of us now, are you?
后邊小屋里有很多工具
There are plenty of tools in the shed out back...
鎬子  鉆機  刨刀
Pickaxe, auger, drawknife...
而你就在那列之中  小姐
and you are somewhere on that list, missy,
就在錘子和鋸子之間的某個地方
somewhere between a hammer and a saw.
屋子的女主人是我的
The lady of the house is mine,
我的女主人
my lady.
你最好別忘了
Now, you best not forget that.
我看我來的真是時候
I see I got here in time
你還沒有淹死這可憐的女孩
before you could drown the poor girl.
或是把她當女巫浸了
Or dunk her as a witch.
緹圖芭
Tituba.
你就這么說你新來的小妹妹嗎
Is that any way to talk about your new little sister?
你做不到  對吧
You couldn't do it, could you?
你看著那雙大眼睛
You looked into those big eyes,
就失去了決心
and you lost your resolve.
我看著那雙眼睛
I looked into those eyes,
在里面看到了我自己
and I saw myself staring back.
然后我就知道了
And then I knew.
還有其他的辦法
There was another way.
她不能指著我大喊女巫
She cannot point at me and say "Witch"
因為她也是其之一
When she's one herself.
剩下的我來吧
I'll finish here.
你知道嗎  梅西
You know, Mercy,
這東西曾經活在大海中
this once lived in the sea,
我們也是如此
as did we.
男人認為他們自己是山石
Men think of themselves as rock,
如石般堅硬
hard as stone.
確實如此
So they are.
堅硬  脆弱
Hard, brittle,
很容易破碎
easily broken.
咱們女人知道自己通常如水
Women know that we are mostly water.
大海在我們周圍
Sea around us...
大海在我們體內
Sea inside us.
當我受傷時
When I hurt,
我會這么想
I remember that.
我會想水的本質
I remember what water is,
想水之所為
what it does.
它流動
It flows.
它改變
It changes.
它比石頭更加有耐性
It endures far longer than the rock.
我知道你今晚有如到地獄走了一遭
Oh, I know you went through hell this night,
我曾經也如此
as I once did.
梅西
Mercy...
你再也不會一個人...
You will never face hell again...
面對地獄了
Alone.
父親
Father?
來吧  孩子
Come, child.
是時候來談談你父親的事了
It's time we talked about your father.